[{"answer": "Are you alright", "docId": "Hesher.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I don't think so. Am I", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I don't know.  Am I bleeding", "docId": "Hesher.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "my friend? Really? Are you sure", "docId": "Hesher.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "OK", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "He's not hungry", "docId": "Hesher.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Yeah, I'm sure", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Not really", "docId": "Hesher.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "What does", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "You did. I heard you", "docId": "Hesher.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Yeah, before that. I asked if you did it. You said", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I said I didn't do it", "docId": "Hesher.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I can't remember what I said", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "What was what", "docId": "Hesher.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Wrong house", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "How old is he", "docId": "Hesher.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Do you know anything about him", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "So is TJ the mouse", "docId": "Hesher.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Well then, what am I", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "No, I'm a grandmother", "docId": "Hesher.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Oh, that's nice. Where are you going", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Yes you are. And you know what grandmother? I'm gonna go on a walk with you in the morning", "docId": "Hesher.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I'm not going anywhere. I'm going with you. Around the block, I guess", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I got the money", "docId": "Hesher.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "The money for the car", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "What money", "docId": "Hesher.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "What money for the car", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I just saved you", "docId": "Hesher.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Only a bit, it's just a cut", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I think we should keep the new one and give them our old one", "docId": "Hesher.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Good. I'm not even sure they know who I am", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I don't know", "docId": "Hesher.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I don't know. I'm sorry", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Where have you been", "docId": "Hesher.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "You lost track of time? It's ten in the morning", "qsentId": 36}]